[{"answer": "Well, honestly when you look at these two men, former President Clinton was a very effusive, excessive guy.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "I mean it all sounds very odd doesn't it?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well I would think probably the happiest person tonight is Hillary Clinton, not to be sitting in the White House as Vice President because in they're in so many trouble right now.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Finally and break to me if you don't mind Candy, I mean is he going to be rather icy when the Vice President arrives for his morning coffee at the White House tomorrow?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Great this is so much fun, I know nothing about this book so you'll get my immediate, spontaneous reaction.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "It looks like Christmas everyday.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Now it's over, Democrats on the right, the President, this book has a more ripping each others throats are, you must be distraught?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I don't think so because the reason Romney lost, well two reasons.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Would it made any difference to Mitt Romney if his running mate have been Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yeah it's in my book.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "It's in their book.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "That does mean it's true?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "It can't.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "But hypothetically if it does?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "It means nothing, it's a reference to Kenya people laugh because the birth (ph) or thing is crazy.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Send him back to Kenya, what does that mean?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "It's clearly not.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Is it clearly a joke?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "I'm not talking about, I mean 50 years ago.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Why are the rules so different with the Democrats?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Is there a nasty sides of the tea party which seeps through with comments like that?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "It's a joke, this is the guy's father.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Does he represent a mindset?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "It always kills because it's silly.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "It's funny really?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No one...", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Silly?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "That's trouble.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What did he have to say about you?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "You're not on everything.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Do you ?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Sure, I hope so, I mean it's very hard to make prediction this far out.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Is it technically possible for a guy like Ted Cruz to be the Republican nominee?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Not on the things he's been talking about, I mean ObamaCare is falling apart right now.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Can he do it with his current policies as he espouses them or will he inevitably have to move more to the center?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, we didn't shut it down.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Was is it worth shutting down the government with all the pain that cost?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I usually, it's my favorite holiday.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Are you going out tonight?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I'm on a book tour, I'm going to home and going to bed.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Are you going to dress up and go down to Sunset Boulevard in some wacky custome?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "It's great, I mean the Red Sox were behind all us victims, the whole time.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Let me ask you first, what was your reaction when you saw the Red Sox winning the World Series in this outpouring of love for Boston Strong?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Sort of really sorry.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What is your condition at the moment?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I mean, to me, it means -- the first responders, the people in our city, I don't take it as -- for us, the victims, I don't feel it fits us.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What does being -- or what does the phrase, \"Boston Strong,\" mean to you?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, I think the message is that, you know, any city can be strong.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "What message would you like it to send, the New York Marathon, to the world if you like?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "You know, I was against the idea, originally, because it just seem like kind of a weird psychedelic song from the '60s where the astronaut dies at the end.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Who told you to do that and how did you feel when you did it?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Just -- yeah.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "Well, what does his e-mail say?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I was really inspired by 2001 Space Odyssey.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Does that over-ride any of the technical things?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "It was this little boy's dream too, Pierce.", "docId": "131031pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "I -- was it only it was cracked up to be when you dreamed of this?", "qSentId": 554}]